( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .club، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
Lin Juan.
لين جوان.
Lin Juan!
لين جوان!
Xia Shang,
شيا شانغ،
this is an arrest warrant.
هذا أمر توقيف.
You're coming with us.
ستأتي معنا.
Mom.
أم.
I was only an accomplice,
لم أكن سوى شريك في الجريمة.
and I gave them the real culprit.
وأعطيتهم الجاني الحقيقي.
My sentence will definitely be lighter than yours.
عقوبتي ستكون بالتأكيد أخف من عقوبتك.
I'll wait outside for you to come out.
سأنتظرك بالخارج حتى تخرج.
Earlier, former Special Administration Bureau member, Lin,
في وقت سابق، قال لين، العضو السابق في مكتب الإدارة الخاصة،
submitted key evidence to the police about Xia Shang's family
قدم أدلة رئيسية للشرطة بشأن عائلة شيا شانغ
running illegal operations in Mugang.
إدارة عمليات غير قانونية في موغان.
The truth about the criminal empire Xia Shang controlled for over a decade,
الحقيقة حول الإمبراطورية الإجرامية التي سيطر عليها شيا شانغ لأكثر من عقد من الزمان،
along with multiple serious crimes, has now come to light.
إلى جانب جرائم خطيرة متعددة، فقد تم الكشف عنها الآن.
Chen Qicheng, a key witness
تشين تشيتشنغ، شاهد رئيسي
who was involved in Xia Shang's criminal group, voluntarily turned himself in.
قام الشخص الذي كان متورطاً في المجموعة الإجرامية لشيا شانغ بتسليم نفسه طواعية.
He gave a detailed account of how Xia Shang used violence
وقدّم سرداً مفصلاً لكيفية استخدام شيا شانغ للعنف
and coercion over the years
والإكراه على مر السنين
to capture Ren and bring them into the Bureau.
للقبض على رين وإحضاره إلى المكتب.
He also revealed the truth
كما كشف الحقيقة
[Qiuxiao Manor Couple Murder Case] behind the Qiuxiao Manor Couple Murder Case five years ago.
[قضية قتل الزوجين في قصر تشيوكسياو] خلف قضية قتل الزوجين في قصر تشيوكسياو قبل خمس سنوات.
The latest results are out.
تم الإعلان عن أحدث النتائج.
Your blood really does contain the missing component.
دمك يحتوي بالفعل على المكون المفقود.
No wonder
لا عجب
my mom woke up
استيقظت أمي
after you gave her a transfusion.
بعد أن قمت بنقل الدم لها.
That component has a special property.
يحتوي هذا المكون على خاصية خاصة.
Once absorbed by the human body,
بمجرد امتصاصها من قبل جسم الإنسان،
it makes a person's voice
إنه يصنع صوت الشخص
become very sharp and high-pitched for a short time.
تصبح حادة وعالية النبرة لفترة قصيرة.
Sharp and high-pitched?
حاد وذو نبرة عالية؟
Miss,
يفتقد،
I've got something fun for you to smell.
لدي شيء ممتع لتشمه.
It...
هو - هي...
I know where it is. Xiaoshan Village.
أعرف مكانها. قرية شياوشان.
I'm heading to Xiaoshan Village right now.
أنا متجه إلى قرية شياوشان الآن.
It was picked up near some satellite wreckage
تم العثور عليه بالقرب من حطام بعض الأقمار الصناعية
behind the village mountain.
خلف جبل القرية.
Only this empty bottle is left.
لم يتبق سوى هذه الزجاجة الفارغة.
Nothing else.
لا شيء آخر.
Xie,
شي،
I'm really sorry.
أنا آسف حقاً.
I've done everything I could.
لقد فعلت كل ما بوسعي.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
[Yiyi] Other researchers helped contact
[ييي] ساعد باحثون آخرون في الاتصال
all the well-known research institutes and labs.
جميع معاهد ومختبرات الأبحاث المعروفة.
None of them has encountered that component.
لم يصادف أي منهم ذلك المكون.
Looks like there's little hope of finding it soon.
يبدو أن الأمل ضئيل في العثور عليه قريباً.
[Nongyu] No need to keep looking.
[نونغيو] لا داعي لمواصلة البحث.
Xiaoshan Village has it.
يوجد ذلك في قرية شياوشان.
[Yiyi] Yay! Freedom at last!
[ييي] ياي! الحرية أخيراً!
[Nongyu] The hospital said
[نونغيو] قال المستشفى
Lin Juan and the others' vital signs are deteriorating rapidly.
تتدهور العلامات الحيوية لـ لين جوان والآخرين بسرعة.
Come straight to the hospital when you're done.
توجه مباشرة إلى المستشفى عند الانتهاء.
Ms. Lin,
السيدة لين،
since my blood contains the missing component from your formula,
بما أن دمي يحتوي على المكون المفقود من تركيبتك،
does that mean
هل هذا يعني
if we extract all of that component
إذا استخرجنا كل هذا المكون
from my body,
من جسدي،
everyone can be saved?
هل يمكن إنقاذ الجميع؟
Nongyu would never agree to that.
لن يوافق نونغيو على ذلك أبداً.
She knows that component has already fused with your blood.
هي تعلم أن هذا المكون قد اندمج بالفعل مع دمك.
If it's all extracted,
إذا تم استخراج كل شيء،
you might fall into a coma like I did before.
قد تدخل في غيبوبة كما حدث لي من قبل.
I understand.
أفهم.
I was just asking.
كنت أسأل فقط.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Sorry to bother you.
أعتذر عن الإزعاج.
How is he now?
كيف حاله الآن؟
Out of danger.
خارج نطاق الخطر.
He just made it through another critical episode.
لقد اجتاز للتو مرحلة حرجة أخرى.
But his condition is changing too fast.
لكن حالته تتغير بسرعة كبيرة.
We can't delay for long.
لا يمكننا التأخير لفترة طويلة.
Good thing
شيء جيد
we've found the missing component.
لقد وجدنا المكون المفقود.
Once the drug is developed,
بمجرد تطوير الدواء،
Lin Juan and the rest will be fine.
لين جوان وبقية الفريق سيكونون بخير.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Did things not go well in Xiaoshan Village?
هل سارت الأمور على نحو سيئ في قرية شياوشان؟
The village chief said
قال رئيس القرية
the gas in that bottle has been used up.
لقد نفد الغاز الموجود في تلك الأسطوانة.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I could use the component in my blood...
يمكنني استخدام المكون الموجود في دمي...
It's okay.
لا بأس.
We still have time.
لا يزال لدينا وقت.
Since we've found it once,
بما أننا وجدناه مرة واحدة،
we can definitely find it again.
يمكننا بالتأكيد العثور عليه مرة أخرى.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
No need to keep looking.
لا داعي لمواصلة البحث.
Really.
حقًا.
There's always been a ready source.
لطالما كان هناك مصدر جاهز.
( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .club، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
I don't want to use a ready source.
لا أريد استخدام مصدر جاهز.
Don't be anxious.
لا تقلق.
The doctor didn't say Lin Juan would die today, right?
لم يقل الطبيب أن لين جوان ستموت اليوم، أليس كذلك؟
We...
نحن...
Let's spend a bit more time looking.
لنقضي بعض الوقت في البحث.
Let's give the doctors more time.
دعونا نمنح الأطباء مزيداً من الوقت.
We can do it.
نستطيع فعلها.
I promise.
أعدك.
We definitely can.
بالتأكيد نستطيع.
Okay.
تمام.
I've just been
لقد كنت للتو
tired and out of my mind.
متعب ومجنون.
Let's get some rest, okay?
لنأخذ قسطاً من الراحة، حسناً؟
How can I be in the mood to rest?
كيف يمكنني أن أكون في مزاج يسمح لي بالراحة؟
And even if we rest,
وحتى لو استرحنا،
what would we do?
ماذا سنفعل؟
I could start pursuing you again.
بإمكاني أن أبدأ بملاحقتك مجدداً.
Then
ثم
you'd have something to do,
سيكون لديك شيء تفعله،
right?
يمين؟
Let's not waste time.
دعونا لا نضيع الوقت.
Let's get back together right now.
فلنعد إلى بعضنا الآن.
Okay.
تمام.
♪A ray of morning sun shines through the cafe curtains♪
♪تتسلل أشعة شمس الصباح عبر ستائر المقهى♪
♪Your fingertips touch the fantasy on the rim of the cup♪
♪تلامس أطراف أصابعك الخيال على حافة الكأس♪
♪The swaying windchime knocks away the time difference♪
♪أجراس الرياح المتأرجحة تزيل فارق التوقيت♪
♪The unread poem waits for a reply♪
♪ القصيدة غير المقروءة تنتظر ردًا ♪
♪Hey, don't plan too far ahead♪
♪مهلاً، لا تخطط للمستقبل البعيد♪
♪The next second might change everything♪
♪ قد تُغير الثانية التالية كل شيء ♪
♪Come on, sway along with the music♪
هيا بنا، تمايلوا مع الموسيقى!
♪Off-key becomes a romantic beat♪
♪يتحول النشاز إلى إيقاع رومانسي♪
♪Showtime♪
♪حان وقت العرض♪
♪Falling into the unknown♪
♪السقوط في المجهول♪
♪Tonight♪
♪الليلة♪
♪I put on a masquerade mask♪
♪ارتديت قناعًا تنكريًا♪
♪Look at you♪
♪انظر إليك♪
♪You remind me of a romance film♪
♪أنتِ تُذكرينني بفيلم رومانسي♪
♪All the night♪
♪طوال الليل♪
♪From sea to shore♪
♪من البحر إلى الشاطئ♪
♪A fate bound to fall♪
♪مصير محتوم♪
♪Into the light♪
♪إلى النور♪
♪Lost in a captivating opera♪
♪ضائع في أوبرا آسرة♪
♪Frozen within♪
♪متجمد من الداخل♪
♪A melody left by the universe♪
لحنٌ تركه الكون
♪In every time and space♪
♪في كل زمان ومكان♪
♪I will meet you again♪
♪سأراك مجدداً♪
♪A ray of morning sun shines through the cafe curtains♪
♪تتسلل أشعة شمس الصباح عبر ستائر المقهى♪
♪Your fingertips touch the fantasy on the rim of the cup♪
♪تلامس أطراف أصابعك الخيال على حافة الكأس♪
♪The swaying windchime knocks away the time difference♪
♪أجراس الرياح المتأرجحة تزيل فارق التوقيت♪
♪The unread poem waits for a reply♪
♪ القصيدة غير المقروءة تنتظر ردًا ♪
♪Hey, don't plan too far ahead♪
♪مهلاً، لا تخطط للمستقبل البعيد♪
♪The next second might change everything♪
♪ قد تُغير الثانية التالية كل شيء ♪
♪Come on, sway along with the music♪
هيا بنا، تمايلوا مع الموسيقى!
♪Off-key becomes a romantic beat♪
♪يتحول النشاز إلى إيقاع رومانسي♪
♪Showtime♪
♪حان وقت العرض♪
♪Falling into the unknown♪
♪السقوط في المجهول♪
♪Tonight♪
♪الليلة♪
♪I put on a masquerade mask♪
♪ارتديت قناعًا تنكريًا♪
♪Look at you♪
♪انظر إليك♪
♪You remind me of a romance film♪
♪أنتِ تُذكرينني بفيلم رومانسي♪
♪All the night♪
♪طوال الليل♪
♪From sea to shore♪
♪من البحر إلى الشاطئ♪
♪A fate bound to fall♪
♪مصير محتوم♪
♪Into the light♪
♪إلى النور♪
♪Lost in a captivating opera♪
♪ضائع في أوبرا آسرة♪
♪Frozen within♪
♪متجمد من الداخل♪
♪A melody left by the universe♪
لحنٌ تركه الكون
♪In every time and space♪
♪في كل زمان ومكان♪
♪I will meet you again♪
♪سأراك مجدداً♪
I might have to go on a long business trip.
قد أضطر للذهاب في رحلة عمل طويلة.
You won't be mad, right?
لن تغضب، أليس كذلك؟
I know
أنا أعرف
we'll definitely find that component.
سنجد هذا المكون بالتأكيد.
The thing is
المسألة هي
Lin Juan and the others can't wait that long.
لا تستطيع لين جوان والآخرون الانتظار كل هذا الوقت.
If it were someone else lying there,
لو كان شخص آخر يرقد هناك،
you might take your time searching.
قد تحتاج إلى بعض الوقت للبحث.
But it was me,
لكن كنت أنا،
you'd be anxious
ستشعر بالقلق
and would find it really fast,
وسيجده بسرعة كبيرة،
right?
يمين؟
I wouldn't be anxious at all.
لن أشعر بالقلق على الإطلاق.
You gave me this job.
لقد منحتني هذه الوظيفة.
I'll only work eight hours a day,
سأعمل ثماني ساعات فقط في اليوم،
and I'm taking weekends off.
وأنا آخذ عطلات نهاية الأسبوع.
But
لكن
I'll do it for a lifetime.
سأفعل ذلك مدى الحياة.
♪You build those castles in the sand♪
♪تبني تلك القصور على الرمال♪
♪And hope with everything you have♪
♪وأمل بكل ما أوتيت من قوة♪
♪The wind is calm tonight...♪
♪الريح هادئة الليلة...♪
This was the last morning I spent with Xie Xinxu
كان هذا آخر صباح قضيته مع شي شينكسو
before he fell into a deep sleep.
قبل أن يغط في نوم عميق.
Later,
لاحقاً،
Mom and I used the component Xie Xinxu contributed
استخدمت أنا وأمي المكون الذي ساهم به شي شينكسو
to develop a special drug for the Affinity virus.
تطوير دواء خاص لفيروس أفينيتي.
When it first went on the market,
عندما طُرحت في السوق لأول مرة،
it sparked a lot of discussion.
أثار ذلك الكثير من النقاش.
[Affinity Special Sustained-Release Capsule]
[كبسولة أفينيتي الخاصة ذات الإطلاق المستدام]
But very soon,
لكن قريباً جداً،
everyone
الجميع
returned to their normal lives,
عادوا إلى حياتهم الطبيعية،
as if those days with Affinity
كما لو أن تلك الأيام مع أفينيتي
had all just been a dream.
كان كل ذلك مجرد حلم.
Why did you throw away my press-on nails?
لماذا رميت أظافري الاصطناعية؟
Those were my favorites.
كانت تلك هي المفضلة لدي.
You left them lying around
لقد تركتهم ملقين في كل مكان
after using them.
بعد استخدامها.
I thought you didn't want them anymore,
ظننت أنك لم تعد تريدهم،
so I threw them away.
لذلك تخلصت منها.
Don't you know press-ons are reusable?
ألا تعلم أن الضمادات اللاصقة قابلة لإعادة الاستخدام؟
Also,
أيضًا،
before throwing them away, couldn't you at least ask me?
قبل التخلص منها، ألا يمكنك على الأقل أن تسألني؟
If you hug me right now,
إذا عانقتني الآن،
I'll forgive you.
سأغفر لك.
♪When hope is hiding♪
♪عندما يختبئ الأمل♪
♪You're fighting for sanity♪
♪أنت تناضل من أجل سلامة عقلك♪
♪Remember you don't have to be alone...♪
تذكر أنك لست مضطرًا لأن تكون وحيدًا...
I threw them away
رميتهم بعيدًا
because I bought you new ones.
لأنني اشتريت لك واحدة جديدة.
♪Gravity holds no weight at all♪
♪الجاذبية لا تحمل أي وزن على الإطلاق♪
♪When help eludes you♪
♪عندما يفلت منك العون♪
♪Call on love…♪
♪استدعِ الحب…♪
Handsome,
وسيم،
have you considered becoming an idol?
هل فكرت في أن تصبح نجمًا؟
Can we exchange contact numbers?
هل يمكننا تبادل أرقام الاتصال؟
We're a legitimate talent agency.
نحن وكالة مواهب مرخصة.
Please look at this.
يرجى الاطلاع على هذا.
What?
ماذا؟
Trainee?
المتدرب؟
Joining a talent show?
هل ستشارك في برنامج مواهب؟
Aren't you too old for that?
ألا تعتبر نفسك كبيراً في السن على ذلك؟
[Juan]
[خوان]
The agency promised they can guarantee I make the finals.
وعدتني الوكالة بأنها تستطيع ضمان وصولي إلى النهائيات.
Go for it then.
انطلق إذن.
You're single anyway,
أنت عازب على أي حال،
you don't smoke, drink, or flirt around.
أنت لا تدخن، ولا تشرب الكحول، ولا تغازل الآخرين.
Zero scandal risk.
لا يوجد خطر من حدوث فضيحة.
Besides,
بجانب،
oh right.
أوه صحيح.
What was that again?
ما هذا مرة أخرى؟
I wish you a center debut.
أتمنى لك بداية موفقة في مركز الملعب.
My friends' lives
حياة أصدقائي
all seem pretty exciting and interesting.
يبدو كل شيء مثيراً للاهتمام وممتعاً للغاية.
Only me,
أنا فقط،
once in a while, I still run into
ما زلت أصادف بين الحين والآخر
these little awkward moments.
هذه اللحظات المحرجة الصغيرة.
All this sincere kindness from everyone
كل هذا اللطف الصادق من الجميع
sometimes makes me confused.
أحياناً يُربكني ذلك.
Xie Xinxu is just sleeping
Xie Xinxu نائم فقط
[Praying Xie Xinxu wakes up soon]
[صلاة Xie Xinxu تستيقظ قريبًا]
and is not actually dead.
وهو ليس ميتاً في الواقع.
Besides,
بجانب،
there's good news.
هناك أخبار سارة.
I was worried that while Xie Xinxu was asleep,
كنت قلقاً من أن شي شينشو كان نائماً،
his baby dragon might be affected.
قد يتأثر تنينه الصغير.
[Suspected discovery of ancient dinosaur traces] Until one day,
[اكتشاف مشتبه به لآثار ديناصورات قديمة] حتى جاء يوم،
[Experts say the photo is AI-generated] I saw a photo
[يقول الخبراء إن الصورة مُولّدة بواسطة الذكاء الاصطناعي] لقد رأيت صورة
on a forum.
في منتدى.
I hope it can live well there.
أتمنى أن يعيش هناك حياة جيدة.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I won't elaborate further on my current life.
لن أسهب في الحديث عن حياتي الحالية.
Thank you for reading this far.
شكراً لكم على قراءة هذا المقال حتى النهاية.
Please allow me
أرجو أن تسمح لي
to make one final, sincere request.
لأقدم طلباً أخيراً وصادقاً.
If your planet has the component
إذا كان كوكبك يحتوي على هذا المكون
we're searching for,
نحن نبحث عن،
and if you're lucky enough
وإذا كنت محظوظاً بما يكفي
to have technology advanced enough
أن تكون التكنولوجيا متقدمة بما فيه الكفاية
to support interplanetary delivery,
لدعم عمليات التوصيل بين الكواكب،
could you please send me some?
هل يمكنك أن ترسل لي بعضاً منها من فضلك؟
At least send it to me
على الأقل أرسلها لي
[A Letter to Extraterrestrial Civilizations] when I still alive.
[رسالة إلى الحضارات خارج الأرض] عندما كنت لا أزال على قيد الحياة.
[Message sent successfully!] Thank you so much.
[تم إرسال الرسالة بنجاح!] شكرًا جزيلًا.
[Earth, 2051]
[الأرض، 2051]
Chairman,
رئيس مجلس الإدارة،
can we help them?
هل يمكننا مساعدتهم؟
This component
هذا المكون
sounds like helium.
يبدو كصوت الهيليوم.
Compile the decoded Planet Y message
قم بتجميع رسالة الكوكب Y التي تم فك شفرتها
into a detailed report.
إلى تقرير مفصل.
I'll submit it to the higher-ups.
سأقدمها إلى المسؤولين الأعلى رتبة.
I'll get right on it.
سأبدأ العمل على ذلك فوراً.
Sorry about that.
أعتذر عن ذلك.
Turn around.
التف حوله.
♪A ray of morning sun shines through the cafe curtains♪
♪تتسلل أشعة شمس الصباح عبر ستائر المقهى♪
♪Your fingertips touch the fantasy on the rim of the cup♪
♪تلامس أطراف أصابعك الخيال على حافة الكأس♪
♪The swaying windchime knocks away the time difference♪
♪أجراس الرياح المتأرجحة تزيل فارق التوقيت♪
♪The unread poem waits for a reply♪
♪ القصيدة غير المقروءة تنتظر ردًا ♪
♪Hey, don't plan too far ahead♪
♪مهلاً، لا تخطط للمستقبل البعيد♪
♪The next second might change everything♪
♪ قد تُغير الثانية التالية كل شيء ♪
♪Come on, sway along with the music♪
هيا بنا، تمايلوا مع الموسيقى!
♪Off-key becomes a romantic beat♪
♪يتحول النشاز إلى إيقاع رومانسي♪
♪Showtime♪
♪حان وقت العرض♪
♪Falling into the unknown♪
♪السقوط في المجهول♪
♪Tonight♪
♪الليلة♪
♪I put on a masquerade mask♪
♪ارتديت قناعًا تنكريًا♪
♪Look at you♪
♪انظر إليك♪
♪You remind me of a romance film♪
♪أنتِ تُذكرينني بفيلم رومانسي♪
♪All the night♪
♪طوال الليل♪
♪From sea to shore♪
♪من البحر إلى الشاطئ♪
♪A fate bound to fall♪
♪مصير محتوم♪
♪Into the light♪
♪إلى النور♪
♪Lost in a captivating opera♪
♪ضائع في أوبرا آسرة♪
♪Frozen within♪
♪متجمد من الداخل♪
♪A melody left by the universe♪
لحنٌ تركه الكون
♪In every time and space♪
♪في كل زمان ومكان♪
♪I will meet you again♪
♪سأراك مجدداً♪